

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Email parmar.nidhir@gmail.com

Mobile (+91) 7984011615

Total work experience
2 Years 5 Months

Social Link https://pnidhir1992.github.io/Knowlage_E ra.github.io/work.html

KEY SKILLS

Product Design

Frontend Development

Front End Design

Figma

Adobe Creative Suite

OTHER PERSONAL DETAILS

City Mumbai

Country India

HOBBIES

Designing

LANGUAGES

Nidhir Parmar

Web and Graphic Designer

PROFILE SUMMARY

My name is Nidhir Parmar. I am a UI/UX & Graphic Designer with over 2.5 years of professional experience in Graphic Design, Photoshop, Illustrator, and Fi kogma. I strongly believe in creating designs that evoke emotion and prioritize client satisfaction. For more than 2.5 years, I have been actively serving the tech community, helping developers enhance their skills in the field of technology. I am always ready to support fellow developer geeks in learning new trends and growing in their careers.

EDUCATION

2013

B.Com

smt j j kundaliya collage

WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2020 - Nov 9

Web and Graphic Designer

Codder Zone

Blend technical skills and creativity to design engaging digital experiences, manage projects, and maintain a strong portfolio.

Nov 2021 - Nov 2022 Web and Graphic Designer

Lets Manage India

As a web and graphic designer, combine technical skills and creativity to craft engaging digital experiences and manage projects.

Nov 2023 -Present

As a Individual Working

Freelancer

As a freelance web and graphic designer, I create visually compelling digital experiences, design user-friendly interfaces, and manage multiple projects with proficiency in design software. I excel in effective communication, stay current with design trends, and deliver high-quality work on time. My strong portfolio reflects my adaptability, creativity, and attention to detail.

- Gujrati
- Hindi
- English

Feb 2024 -Present UI UX and Graphic Designer

Codemegan technologies

Designed user-friendly UI/UX interfaces for web and mobile, increasing user engagement by 15% and reducing bounce rate by 20%. Created captivating graphic designs that boosted brand awareness by 25%. Collaborated with crossfunctional teams to deliver innovative concepts on time and exceed client expectations.

Projects

24 Months

Money Transfer

- Managed a Money Transfer project for 24 months, resulting in a 20% increase in successful transactions.

5 Months

Florena Cosmetic

my key responsibilities is to develop website and manage other services for behalf of them

3 Months

Paper Cup Manufachering

in this project we mainte and develope Comapny web from scrach and also do social media management and Digital Marketing